(light upbeat music)
- [Sam] Get ready for a "Game Changer"!
Tonight's guests: control the crowd,
it's Jacquis Neal!
(Jacquis shushing)
The host with the most blackmail,
Lily Du!
(crowd cheering)
"They won't give me back
the company credit card," Vic Michaelis!
The drunker she gets,
the more sober she appears?
Ele Woods!
(crowd cheering)
And AKA BDG LOL, Brian David Gilbert!
- Ooh!
- Modest.
- And your host, me.
I've been here the whole time.
This is "Game Changer", the only game show
where the game changes every show.
I am your host, Sam
Reich, I am joined today
by these five lovely contestants.
Now, you all understand
how the game works.
- This is my first time.
- No.
- Sam.
- That's right, our players have no idea
what game it is they're about to play.
The only way to learn is by playing.
The only way to win is by learning,
and the only way to begin is by beginning.
So without further ado, let's begin.
Players, please take your glasses
as well as your paddles and pens
and stand in front of the velvet rope.
- Wow.
- Oh.
- [Lily] Well, I can't see
out of these glasses, Sam.
Sorry, everyone has
their glasses on, right?
- Yeah.
- You all are wearing them?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Sure.
- Perfect, and one more step forward.
- Okay, now take a bow.
- And turn.
There you go, perfect.
- Stay, stay there for now.
- We're ready to begin.
- Players, a bit of an art
history question for you.
Does anyone recognize this image?
(light accordion music)
- Yeeessss-ah.
- That's Georges Seurat.
- Oh yeah.
- That's stunning!
- That's right, "A Sunday Afternoon-
- Wow.
- "On the Island of
La Grande Jatte" by Georges Seurat,
arguably the most famous
example of pointillism.
- Pointillism.
- Yeah.
- But to recognize a painting
and really observe it
are two entirely different
things, don't you think?
- One dollar, I'll take it for one dollar.
- I thought-
- Huh? Oh.
(crew laughing)
- One dollar.
- I spy with my little eye
something that will be returned
for a refund once shooting is over.
- Oh.
- What?
- The umbrella, maybe.
- Okay.
- It's so interesting
that you're calling it an umbrella
because words matter, right?
- Vic wrote parasol.
(Sam and crew laughing)
- Actually! I-
- Vic's standing in front
of me and Vic's really tall.
- I wrote what I think is being returned.
- Yeah, I know what's going back.
- [Lily] We're sure it's not the monkey?
You don't think that's returnable?
- Well, that is handmade.
- That feels too easy.
- What about that pipe?
- That is not a pipe!
"Ceci n'est pas une pipe."
- [Vic] But that's like got paint on it,
you know what I'm saying?
- Yeah, it's okay,
Amazon will take it back.
- There's some paint.
- Amazon will take it back.
(Sam laughing)
- Players, please reveal your answers
by turning around your
paddles in three, two, one.
Jacquis, what'd you say?
- Dat ass.
- Dat ass. Lily?
- I said umbrella, and
you know what I mean.
- Vic?
- I said parasol.
- We're on a team.
- Ele.
- Un parapluie.
- Oh, French.
- Of course.
- I wrote Bilbo's pipe 'cause
that thing is well crafted.
- Tableau players, please reveal.
(drum rolling)
(chiming music)
(audience exclaims)
It is in fact
the umbrella or parasol.
- Wow.
- Woo!
Yup, come on.
- La merde!
- [Sam] Lily, Vic, and Ele,
because all three of you
picked the correct answer,
that's three eyeballs for each of you.
- What?
- Three eyeballs for each of us.
- Is that gonna be the prize all the time?
Do I have to keep doing this?
(Sam and crew laughing)
- I spy with my little eye an anachronism.
- Sam, I went to art school.
I don't know what these words mean.
- [Brian] I was gonna say
the earring seems maybe...
But they had gold earrings back then.
- We're not allowed to get any closer?
- That's not anachronistic.
- You can switch positions
behind the velvet rope,
but you cannot cross the velvet rope.
- What is the-
- Do you want us
to hold you back so that way you can get-
- Yes!
- Yeah, yeah.
Okay, ready? Here we go.
- Oh, maybe, okay, ready?
Okay, got it, we're good?
- It's prop two.
- You take a hand, Brian.
- Here, I'll just hold onto
the belt loop.
- It's prop number 2.
- Huh?
- We're good.
We're just making sure it's good.
- My brother right there
got some dope-ass earrings.
- Wait, wait, let's ask, let's ask.
- Yeah.
- (whispering) Hey.
- Hey.
- Hey brother, I know these white people
told you don't talk, but talk to me.
(crew laughing)
I know they told you don't say nothing.
- We're not sure.
- Oh, no, guys, the glasses!
The glasses!
- Oh he has (indistinct)
- You're so right-
- Okay.
- It is the glasses.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait,
But, but I think we should
all guess a couple things.
- Can Jacquis and I write glasses
'cause I think it's the right one
and I wanna get some eyeballs?
- That's a great idea.
- Can I do that?
- I'll go with the earring.
- No, you should go with the earring.
- Players, please reveal your
answers in three, two, one.
Jacquis.
- Glasses.
- Lily.
- Man earring.
You know what I mean.
- Vic.
- Glasses.
- Ele.
- Earrings.
- Brian.
- Glasses.
- Let's reveal.
(drum rolling)
It is in fact the pipe.
- Pipe?
- The pipe!
- Wow.
- It is a-
- Vape?
- Vape pipe.
- What? Oh, come on, man!
- No eyeballs that round, I'm afraid.
- That's okay, now we know-
- No eyeballs?
- What we're playing today.
- Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I spy with my little eye:
my cousin.
- Hey, my man, I know these
white people told you...
- [Brian] Okay.
- But are you related to...
No, okay.
(all laughing)
Is anybody under this dress?
- Legally, if somebody's under the dress,
you have to tell us.
- Yeah.
(Sam laughing)
- Maybe it's just like
a stool or something.
This man looks too much
like Sam, so that's not him.
- Okay.
- It's not him, no.
- I think she's a really good option.
- Yes.
- [Brian] Parasol lady.
- I think it could be the monkey
'cause we all come from the monkey.
- I agree.
- Now when he says like,
"Reveal yourselves," how is
that monkey gonna reveal itself?
- This, yes-
- Players, please
lock in your answers.
- Okay.
- We should all guess different.
- Yeah, that sounds good.
- I'm going with the lady.
- Please reveal your
answers in three, two, one.
- I said the monkey.
- [Lily] I said the Black gentleman.
- Pipe guy.
- Lady!
- Parasol woman.
- Would my cousin please
reveal themselves?
(drum rolling)
- Sammy.
(all exclaiming)
- It is the woman!
- Judy!
- Dang it!
- She does look like Sam!
- That's so true.
- Man!
- -so much for doing this.
- I'm out-thinking myself.
- That's sweet.
- How close are you with Sam?
- Wow.
- His dad is my first cousin.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
- Gotcha, gotcha.
- Very fun.
- Hello.
- Permission to brag
about you for a moment.
- Please.
- Judy, was an agent
for cinematographers, now works
in the visual effects industry.
- Wow.
- Whoa!
- Nico and Ash, we can go ahead
and add two eyeballs for each of them.
Players I spy with my little eye: cake.
- Oh, come on.
- Now, listen.
- Okay, okay.
- It's dat ass, y'all.
I know I was doing a bit so far-
- I think that-
- But that is ass is cake,
that's some cake right there.
- That rose looks a lot like cake to me.
- Oh!
- Ooh, the rose.
Is it cake? Okay, yes.
- I think the monkey's also pretty good.
- It's got to be the monkey 'cause it-
- It's the monkey.
- Has the cake holder.
- Let's all do the
monkey, let's all do it.
- No, because then somebody
doesn't lose points.
- Okay, okay, okay.
(Sam laughing)
Jacquis, write that out.
- Wait, can somebody wheelbarrow me?
- Yeah.
- Can somebody wheelbarrow me after?
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- Okay, forward.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
- Forward.
- Here we go, feet, feet.
- [Jacquis] Right there, right there.
Right there.
- That's good, that's good.
- Wait, wait, somebody hold my waist.
- I got you.
- Somebody hold my waist.
- Here we go, dip.
(Lily grunts)
- Okay.
- All right.
- Now pick me back up.
- Please reveal your
answers in three, two, one.
- Da monkey.
- That monkey.
- The monkey.
- De monkey.
- Monkey.
- Let's go ahead
and reveal this cake.
- Ash, Nico, please.
- Is it booty?
- Oh!
- It's the booty!
- No!
- It was dat ass!
- Jacquis!
- No!
- Oh my god!
You're killing me!
- Oh!
- Wait, wait, wait-
- I'm so mad.
- Permission for Jacquis
to eat it from the sword.
- That ass, oh my god.
- Dat ass, dammit!
- [Brian] That's a fork? You have a-
- [Jacquis] You know, I
made it a bit too much
that it-
- Ooh!
- [Lily] They made the
monkey look like cake.
- [Jacquis] I would like some ass.
- Guys, this cake-
- Just with our hands?
- It looks good to me.
- The layer of chocolate...
- That's some good ass.
- It's okay.
Plate's not cake.
- That's good.
- Thank you to Nico and Ash. Let's hear it
for our tableau players.
(contestants applauding)
- Bravo, bravo.
- Brava.
- Fantastic.
- A masterpiece.
- The points as we head
into round two of our game,
Jacquis with zero-
- Oh.
- Lily with three, Vic with three,
Ele with five, and Brian with two.
It's time for our next tableau.
- I'm excited.
- Dang.
(players exclaiming)
- Wow!
- Ah, yes, the signing
of the Declaration of Independence,
when America was just a fragile idea and--
oh wait, it still is.
- Oh my god.
- But be warned, players,
in this next round,
one of you could be...
the spy.
- What?
- No.
- The spy earns points
by other players voting with
them on the wrong answer.
- No.
- Please put on
your googly eyeglasses, players.
- My lashes are literally so long,
it keeps the glasses from
getting too close to my eyes.
- [Lily] You can take away my vision, but-
- No, don't touch me!
- [Lily] But you can't
take away my hearing.
- [Vic] What do you mean?
- [Jacquis] No, you listening for feet,
'cause Sam is historically-
- She's always listening.
- Is this gonna be a fake
thing where there's no spy?
- I feel like that's -
- Oh, oh, Sam!
Sam's tickling me!
- Stop tickling her!
Sam, stop it!
- Players-
- Stop it, Sam!
- Please take down your glasses.
I spy with my little eye
a hidden human hand.
- There's a glove right by this-
- [Brian] That's what I
was gonna say, but that's-
- Well, the candelabras are hands.
- Oh, shoot the candelabras-
- Oh yeah.
- Oh, that's his hand for sure!
- [Jacquis] But that's not a human hand.
- [Ele] No, it wouldn't be
upside-down like that.
- It's a glass hand.
- Hidden human hand.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, I get it!
The person in the red is
hiding her human hand.
- Okay, I am like 90% sure they want us
to choose one of those golden hands.
- Right.
- Which makes me want
to choose something completely different.
- I think it's the Power Ranger hands.
- [Brian] The Power Ranger hands?
- [Jacquis] They are hidden hands.
- Okay.
- Players, please-
- Lock in your answers.
- Power Ranger hand I'm doing as well.
- Players, please reveal your answers.
Jacquis.
- Power Ranger hand.
- [Sam] Lily.
- I think one of those, yeah,
white gloves on the
table has a hand in it.
- Vic.
- There is a human hand
in one of those white gloves.
- [Sam] Ele.
- That golden taper-
- Are those gloves too?
- [Ele] Hand is a hand.
- Brian.
- Power Ranger gloves.
- Let's reveal in three, two, one.
(drum rolling)
(music chiming)
(players exclaiming)
(Lily shrieking)
- That was my guess.
- And is it that guy's?
- Mwah!
- That is my guess.
- That is Vic and Lily
with the correct answer.
Would our spy please take a bow?
- Hey.
- Oh!
- Brian who voted on the incorrect answer
with Jacquis.
- You got me to...
You said I could answer-
- You said it first.
- That is points for you, which means-
- Dang.
- Two eyeballs for Lily,
two eyeballs for Vic, and
one spy ball for Brian.
- Spy ball?
- You got something special.
- A spy ball.
- Spy Kids.
- Spy ball.
- Players, please put
on your googly eye glasses now.
- This is crazy.
- Don't worry.
- That rocked.
- The table is covered
with a curtain.
- Yeah.
- There's cake under the table.
- [Vic] There's always
cake under the table,
so we've got to be weary that
there is gonna be something
hiding from us that will have a mechanism.
- Ow, Sam, stop pinching me!
- Players, the spy has
not remembered that I need
for them to take their glasses off.
So I'm back at my podium...
(players laughing)
To affirm that that needs to happen.
- God bless.
Oh, we're doing it.
- [Jacquis] I think we know.
- [Lily] That's very placed, very...
- Players, if I could please
have you take your glasses off.
I spy with my little eye
someone not in a wig.
- Oh.
- Someone not in a wig.
- Oh boy.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh!
- I feel like it's gotta be
Power Ranger, right?
- That's what it'd look like.
- No, I think
that's the obvious one.
- I will say this man is wearing a wig.
- Yeah, the actor on the
end is wearing a wig.
I could see my man sitting
down not having fake hair.
- Yeah.
- [Lily] His hairline
looks real, but the woman's
hairline looks so real.
- That's a boxy hairline.
- Okay.
- This has got to be
men's biggest insecurity-
- I think it's the ponytail.
- To get their hairline ogled.
(Sam and Jacquis laughing)
(crew laughing)
- Players, please reveal your answers.
Jacquis.
- The man sitting down.
- Lily.
- The woman.
- Vic.
- The person under the table.
(Ele gasps)
Meaning that if the person
under the table isn't wearing a wig,
just because we can't see
them, I still get a point.
- Um, that is...
- Vic has played a lot
of Game Changer.
- Ele wrote that
it's the woman, it must not be the woman.
- I'm saying Red Power Ranger.
- That's the lady.
- Yeah.
- I'm fucked.
- Red Power Ranger.
- I wanna change my answer.
- Who is not wearing a wig?
Reveal yourself in three, two, one.
(drum rolling)
- Man.
(all exclaiming)
Yeah!
- No!
- Yes!
- Real hair!
- That is going to be
one point for Jacquis.
- Just to confirm,
the person under the
table is wearing a wig?
- Vic, I hate to do this,
you are technically correct.
- Aw!
- Yeah!
- [Sam] I will give you a point as well,
even though that was not my intention.
- Yeah.
- Yep, entire streaming service.
- Will our spy please reveal themselves
by taking a bow?
- So that's two points
'cause me and Vic were right.
- It was me,
but I did mess it up and I
didn't remember how to play.
- Nonetheless, Ele, that is-
- You crushed.
- Two spy balls for you.
Thank you, Nico and Ash.
- I'll take it.
- Players, please put on your glasses now.
- I should have looked
at what Ele was writing
in the last minute 'cause we...
- I really messed that up, I'll admit it.
Because he kept tapping me and
so I was confused, you know?
- [Jacquis] You wouldn't
take your glasses off.
Lily-
- Should I try
and draw something with the blindfold on?
- Ooh, that's a great idea.
- What do you want me
to try and draw?
- Charlie Brown.
- Players, please remove
your googly eyeglasses.
- Okay.
- I spy with my little eye
a piece of Hollywood memorabilia.
- Okay, well, it's the
Power Ranger gloves.
- Or it's the shine,
the six-cent shine box?
- [Ele] But it wouldn't be that obvious?
- "The Sixth Sense" shine box?
- This is old.
- A shine box, that's good.
- Was that in "The Sixth Sense"?
- All right, what's that egg?
- Oh, that's that-
- Ooh, "Jurassic Park"!
- No, that's, ooh!
Does it have a mosquito in it?
- [Lily] It's amber.
- Also the goblet-
well, okay, here's the thing.
Do we think Dropout has the money to get
a goblet from "Indiana Jones"?
- [Sam] That's a question.
- I don't know.
- Yes, they paid
Howie Mandel so much money.
- I think that might be the "Titanic" gem.
- Okay.
- [Vic] I really don't think
so, that looks pretty cheap.
- Players, please lock in your answers.
- Okay.
- All right.
- We've been saying Power Ranger gloves.
I'm gonna go Power Ranger gloves.
- Yeah.
- And show them to me
in three, two, one.
- Jacquis.
- The Power Ranger gloves.
- Lily.
- The "Titanic" diamond.
- The Power Ranger gloves.
- The PR gloves.
- Shoe shine box.
- Please reveal yourself
in three, two, one.
(drum rolling)
- Yeah.
- Yes!
- I mean, there's no way
those were in the painting.
- Ele, I do think we need
to confer that you know
how the spy works.
- Ele, are you the spy?
Ele!
(players laughing)
- Ele, you just gave us points
and you don't get points.
- I didn't remember how it worked.
- You know what it is!
- You have to get people
to guess with you on the wrong answer.
- Oh, with me.
- Yeah.
- Actually, Ele, I think
you're doing a great job and I-
- Thank you so much, Ele.
- I needed those three balls.
- Players, we own the
Hero Ranger red gloves
from the "Mighty Morphin
Power Rangers" movie, 1995.
- The '95 one?
- Wow.
- And all of the rest of these props
are totally and completely fake.
That is gonna be two eyeballs for Jacquis,
that is gonna be two eyeballs-
- Isn't it three?
- No.
- Because Ele guessed it too
even though she was the spy.
(overlapping chatter)
- I could use a point.
- Vic, I feel like you've caught me
on a technicality again.
- I could use a point.
- Literally, who cares?
I'm just saying technically-
- I could use-
- All right.
- Three of us guessed it.
- Nico and Ash,
we are gonna say three for Jacquis-
- Yes!
- Three for Vic.
- Only if that feels fair.
- And three for me.
- That's so many!
- And zero
for Ele, I'm afraid.
- No, no, no, no,
I get three too.
- No.
- I got it right, so lie?
- [Sam] Thank you, Nico and Ash.
- Take three away from Ele.
- Players, please put on your glasses now.
- Okay.
- Pick Ele again.
- Yeah, please.
- [Brian] It can't be Ele again.
- What should I draw?
- Okay, are we all drawing this time.
- Nerd!
- Draw feet.
- Everybody draw feet.
- Okay.
- Everybody.
- And if you didn't draw feet,
it's because you were panicking.
- And you are trying-
- No, Sam,
don't touch my feet, ow!
- All right players,
please remove your glasses.
- That's pretty good.
- I spy with my little eye-
- Yeah.
- Cake.
- Cake, oh.
- Oh, come on now.
What's under the table?
- Sam.
- Oh, okay, okay, it's dat ass.
- What ass?
(crew laughing)
- I don't know, it's some ass under there.
- [Brian] I think it's one of the hands,
one of the hand candle holders.
- Yeah, it could be.
- But that would be hard to put a candle
in it though.
- Yeah, the weight-
- [Vic] But that's kind of it.
- [Brian] I think it's
the entire hat rack.
- [Jacquis] I think it's the table.
- It's that candle holder
'cause it's been moving
'cause you can see the base is painted up
on the arm a little bit,
and there is a ceramic
thing where the candle is.
- Vic's the spy then.
- And please reveal
your answers to me in three, two, one.
Jacquis?
- The goblet.
- That's so kind.
- Lily.
- Gold telescope.
- [Sam] Vic.
- I'm going with the hand.
- [Sam] Ele.
- I'm also going with the hand.
- I think Ele's the spy. Now I'm worried.
- I think it's the
gold telescope, but I
think Lily's the spy.
- I didn't even know you wrote telescope.
- Without further ado,
let's reveal this cake.
- If it's the ass of the
person under the table,
I'm gonna lose my mind.
(drum rolling)
- Ooh.
(all exclaiming)
- No, a candle?
- A candle!
- What?
- Let us try!
- It got something at that
(clamoring for cake)
- Let us try!
- Oh, okay.
- These little orphans
trying their best...
Oh my gosh.
(Sam clears throat)
- Wow, it's electric at the bottom.
- It's electric.
- Will our spy
please take a bow.
There was no spy.
(group disappointment)
- Oh my god.
- That's why it was so fast and efficient.
- That is no points for
any of you, I'm afraid.
- Dang.
- Tough.
- Please give a round of
applause to our tableau players.
- Bravo.
- Thank you so much.
- Amazing.
- Bravo!
- Amazing work.
- Players, the points as
we head into round three:
Jacquis with four, Vic
with nine, Lily with five,
Ele with seven, and Brian with three.
- Anyone's game.
- Brian.
- It's time for our next tableau.
(gentle music)
- Wow!
(players exclaiming)
- You both look beautiful!
- A 1950s couple gathered
around the television
for a wholesome evening of watching me
ruin people's lives in black and white.
- That's so funny.
- But be careful, players.
In the next round, there could be more
than one spy working against each other.
- Oh, what?
- What do you mean
against each other?
- Explain this one more time for Ele.
- Two spies may not
vote for the same thing
and both get points.
Players, please put on
your googly-eye glasses.
- They're both closeted.
- All right, googly eyes.
- [Sam] And prepare for a tap from me.
- [Brian] Okay.
- [Vic] What do you think their-
- I love this tableau.
- ...relationship is to each other?
In love?
- Okay, what do we wanna draw?
- Mona Lisa.
- Mona Lisa?
- Okay.
- Mona Lisa, let's do it.
- Okay, so she's smiling,
she's mysterious.
- Oh my gosh, Sam, stop poking Lily.
- No, I liked that one.
- Okay.
- That was good.
- Oh god,
I'm not gonna get her
smile right, I know that.
- I've already-
- Players-
- Is she in The Louvre?
- Please-
- Yes.
- Why didn't they steal her?
- Take down your glasses.
I spy with my little eye
something illegal in California.
- I think I know what this is,
but I'm wondering if it's too obscure.
- What is this?
- What?
- So there's like a big
thing about lobster fishing
and lobster trapping in California.
- Oh.
- And so I am wondering
- There are no lobsters-
- There is a lobster hidden-
- Off the coast of California.
- Vic is a spy, let's go ahead
and say that-
- That is crazy.
- Yeah, I stopped listening
to Vic immediately.
- To maybe-
- Wait, do you think in
his little cigarette,
there could be something that's not weed?
- Oh, is there ivory?
- Fentanyl.
- There is possible...
- Yeah.
- There's cocaine in there?
- Is there ivory
on the set somewhere?
- Ooh.
- Oh yes.
- Ivory inlay.
- Good idea.
- Ivory inlay potentially
one the Le Creuset on the bottom.
- Ah.
- (gasps) Oh my god, there is!
- Oh, the throwing stars.
- [Brian] Oh, you're
right, it's gotta be those.
- Wait, those are legal
in California.
- It's gotta be the shurikens.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
- Oh, you would know.
- Brass knuckles are
not legal in California.
- That, I know.
- Throwing stars and...
Brass knuckles are not legal anywhere.
- I did weapons class this year.
- Players, show them to me.
- I said the throwing stars.
- Lily.
- The Creuset.
- Vic.
- I said ivory.
- Ele.
- I said the throwing stars.
- Brian.
- I said the ninja weapons
'cause there's also other ones over there.
- Let's reveal in three, two, one.
(drum rolling)
- Yeah!
- [Ele] Oh my god! (screams)
(all laughing)
- You're not allowed, only we're allowed
to do that to Sam!
- Yes it's the throwing stars.
- [Brian] We just learned
how illegal that was.
- If you kill me on camera,
you have to blur my face-
- Would our spies-
- For my funeral.
- Please take a bow.
- I don't think we should take a bow.
- Oh, and the two people who
didn't say throwing star.
- Yeah, you know it's us!
- Nico and Ash, that is three eyeballs
for Jacquis, Ele, and Brian.
Players, please put on-
- Liar.
- Your googly eyeglasses
and prepare for...
- Okay.
- Oh, okay.
- [Brian] All right, what
are we drawing this time?
- Sam.
- Oh, good idea, good idea.
- Oh.
- Here we go.
- No, not me.
- Sam, okay.
- Here we go.
- Ow, Sam, your mouth is so wet.
- [Brian] How does his hair look?
- Sam's hair?
- What's his deal?
- Okay.
- Players, please
remove your glasses.
- That's not too bad.
- Oh!
- Wait, mine's good.
- I spy with my little eye
something the art team
sourced 10 minutes ago.
- [Vic] I know the big box
store that shirt came from.
- Everything on this set is black
and white except that blue cat.
- Oh, that's-
- You think that's something
they sourced 10 minutes ago?
- Yeah.
- They got a blue...
He is such a find.
- Yeah, absolutely.
You can run down here,
there's like a bunch
of thrift stores around here.
- Bunch of props here.
- [Brian] We can absolutely...
- [Brian] I have seen, I could promise...
- Oh god!
- Oh no!
- I'm stuck!
- Yeah, Vic, you're not gonna
end up on the other side, (laughs) no.
- [Jacquis] No, Vic.
(Jacquis and Sam laughing)
- To be technically-
- Wait, Vic,
look at the flowers!
- For that to be...
Vic, I wanna be very clear.
For that to be technically allowed,
your head would need to be
on the other side of the velvet rope.
That's how that bit would make sense.
- But what if we're doing-
- Back.
- A two-step?
- Okay.
- Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- I had my answer before this.
- Please lock in
your answers, players.
- I feel like the flowers
you just get from any flower shop.
- Players, please reveal your
answers in three, two, one.
- Bam.
- Jacquis.
- El gato blue.
- Didn't keep it going in Spanish.
- Lily.
- Cake 'cause Ele said cake.
- [Brian] Okay.
- I believe in our art
department and I believe
that they would not put a
time-period inaccurate boa
in the back there unless they
were under duress by Sam Reich.
- Vic, a couple of times now,
maybe correct or maybe
slighting the art department.
Ele.
- No, I said
I believe in the art department.
- Ele.
- I said cake
because Lily said cake.
- And Brian.
- Blue cat.
- Let's please reveal
what was sourced by the
art department today.
- Brian might be tricking me.
- Ooh, what is revealing?
(drum rolling)
(all exclaiming)
- It was the newspaper!
- Oh, Jesus Christ!
- Newspaper!
- I'm a fucking idiot.
- And players, here, in
case there's any doubt,
is our production staff
picking this up 10 minutes ago.
- Hey, art department,
I just wanted to say,
(Sam and crew laughing)
I love you guys.
- That is unfortunately-
- This was a joke.
- No points for anyone. Except,
would our spy please take a bow?
- I think Brian is a spy.
- Why?
- 'Cause he used me again, you used me.
You used me-
- Lily, are you
raising your hand?
- You said my confidence...
- Yeah, who else?
- Lily is the spy?
Who else is the spy?
- No one.
- Raise your hand, bro.
- Just Lily?
- Just the one.
- Just Lily? Okay, I'm sorry.
- You're just, hey, that was
stupid, that's all right.
- One spy ball for Lily.
Thank you, Nico and Ash.
Players, please put on your eye glasses.
- Okay.
- This is so fun.
- This is great.
- Okay.
- Okay, what are we drawing?
- What about the State of Indiana?
- The State of Indiana?
- Oh, that'd be so hard.
- Yeah, the state shape of Indiana.
- Yeah, I can do...
- [Lily] I don't know the shape-
- Then you just gotta guess.
- Of anything.
- And glasses down, players.
I spy with my little eye
a prop from "Game Changer" season one.
- Okay, the ducks are definitely...
I remember ducks being important
in "Game Changer" just-
- So we are watching-
- Yeah, it's the show.
- We are sorta watching-
- I was not, sorry,
is this season one?
- It's not the vase, the
vase is a red herring
'cause that was one of
the first ones, I think.
And the vase is broken,
and I do genuinely think
that that's a red herring.
- What vase, that bowl?
- Where it's like, Sam has-
- A vase was more recent.
- It's like one of the first
big viral clips from "Game Changer"
where Sam's got the
vase and they were like,
"Make that noise," and he drops the vase.
(ceramic crashes)
- You don't think the vase looks kind
of like broken and glued back together?
- But that's why I'm saying
I think it's a red herring.
- Oh, it was broken, I see.
- I just wanna say I have
seen season one and I don't know.
- Hey, Ele, thanks for
checking out the work.
- I'm paying $12 a month for Dropout.
- Players, please lock in your answer
and show them off in three, two, one.
- Bam, the vase.
- Lily.
- The vase.
- Oh, I thought it was
maybe a double red herring
and I said the vase.
(Sam laughing)
- Ele.
- The TV.
- [Sam] And Brian.
- I did the vase.
- Okay, this is making me feel
like maybe we're in trouble.
- We might be in trouble.
- Let's reveal the prop from
"Game Changer" season one now.
- The cigarette?
- Oh.
(drum rolling)
- I get it,
he's gonna break the vase.
- Ooh!
- [Lily] He's gonna break the vase.
(all cheering)
- Yeah! Yeah!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
- Wow!
- Oh man!
- Yeah!
- Would our spy please take a bow?
- No spy, I guess?
- No spy.
- That is four eyeballs-
- Wow.
- For Jacquis.
- Are you surprised I know that?
Yeah, I watch the show.
- And Brian.
- But wait, it's showing right now!
- Players, please put on
your googly-eye glasses now.
- Okay, what do we wanna draw?
- Everyone draw Pikachu.
- Pikachu.
- Oh, good one.
- Exactly.
But I don't think it's
gonna look close enough, so-
- I think mine definitely will.
- "Pika-chu!"
I feel like if you-
- "A-chu!"
- Make it look not like
Pikachu enough, then it's fine.
- Yeah, that's a really good one.
- Players, please take
your glasses down now.
- Okay.
- That's pretty good.
- I spy with my little eye cake.
- Oh.
(Brian grunting)
- It's cake, it's cake.
- [Lily] Yes, I think he's
tricking us like the ass.
- Where's the frame on this?
The frame.
- Vic, do you mean the shot?
- The shot, where's the frame?
- The shot-
- The shot, where's the shot?
- The shot is above you.
- It's above you.
You want me to hold you back?
- Ah, okay,
where are we getting, are we
getting full frame in there?
- We're getting full frame.
- Then I'm ready to answer.
You are getting the fucking...
(Sam laughing)
- I got you, I got you, I got you.
- I think it's the cake.
- Please-
- You are getting the full shot.
- [Brian] Is the cake the cake?
- You are getting the full shot, correct?
Okay, I'm ready.
- All right.
(Sam and crew laughing)
- Thank you.
- I don't think it's...
- Please reveal your answers-
- The candle is covered in wax.
- In three, two, one.
- I think cake is cake.
- Lily?
- I think it's cake.
- Vic?
- I think it's the microphone.
(Jacquis and crew laughing)
- You think it's the microphone?
- I believe so strongly
that the art department...
(Sam laughing)
Would not let a microphone...
- Vic's somehow both
simultaneously underestimating
and overestimating my art department.
And Ele.
- I wrote the "caké,"
which is different than cake.
- And Brian.
- Just the cake.
Let's reveal the cake.
- I said the caké.
- Okay.
(drum rolling)
- The blue cat.
- Oh my god it's the blue cat!
- No! No!
- I keep saying
the right things!
- Oh my god,
I should get points for that.
- I keep choosing something
that's gonna be cake!
- Bitch, why'd you write cake?
- Why'd you write cake?
- 'Cause I spent the whole-
- I spent the whole game trying
to convince them it was the cake!
- But why are you coming over to me?
- Do not let this man Marie Antoinette us.
Sam, can you take a bite
of the microphone for me?
- Can I take a bite of the cake?
- That is wild.
- Just from this side?
- That looks so nice.
- Or is the whole thing cake?
- [Sam] The whole thing's chocolate.
- [Brian] That's beautiful.
- Wait, so it's chocolate?
- I'll eat this paw.
- [Brian] Oh my gosh.
- That is going to be no
points for any of our players.
Would our spies please take a bow?
Let's get a round of applause
for our tableau players.
- Woo! Bravo!
- Wonderful work.
- [Jacquis] Goodbye.
- The points as we head into round four:
Jacquis with 11, Lily
with 10, Vic with 13,
Ele with 10, and Brian with 10.
And with that, it's time
for our next tableau.
- [Jacquis] It is!
- Oh my god!
- You nailed it.
- It's "Dogs Playing Poker".
C.M. Coolidge painted this
scene more than a century ago,
showing that long before TikTok,
people liked dogs doing people things.
Take comfort, players, because one of you-
- Yeah.
- May now be an informant.
- Oh boy.
- What?
- The informant knows the identity
of one spy.
- Okay.
- Say that again to Ele.
Say it again to Ele.
- Spy?
- Yeah?
- Okay.
- Spy.
- Informant.
- Oh, it's a rat.
- A rat, I would never rat on you.
- Players, please put on your glasses.
- What are we drawing?
- Let's draw somebody pinching somebody.
- Okay.
- A pinch?
- [Brian] "Draw somebody
pinching somebody," that's...
- You might like it.
Ow, that's really hard, Sam!
(Jacquis laughing)
- [Jacquis] Sam, did you smack-
Lily's butt?
- Sam, did you smack Lily?
- Wow.
- Okay, I don't know
how this is gonna work.
- [Jacquis] This is, y'all are...
- This is-
- What?
- Yeah, I don't know.
- [Lily] I feel like when people...
- Okay.
- I don't know, 'cause Lily-
- What?
- Lily's been a spy a lot.
- Three times in a row.
- Lily continues to be spy.
- Players, please take down your glasses.
- Yes.
- I spy with my little eye-
- [Jacquis] Okay.
- Something featuring an earlier tableau.
- Ooh, okay, I love this.
- I will come clean immediately.
I am the informant and I
know that Ele is the spy.
- Oh, I know what it is.
- What?
- I know what it is.
- What is it?
- [Jacquis] It's the clock.
It's clock and it's on 10:10 again.
- Is it?
- Oh, do you mean
that's the-
- What clock is that from?
- Well, well, let's all just
all watch what Vic does next.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- I'm the informant.
- Well, but would they say that
if they were the informant-
- I don't know.
- Or if they were the spy?
- What do you think it is?
- Yeah, Ele, what do you think it is?
- Yeah.
- Okay, well,
the cake is really dynamic.
- The cake is dynamic?
I think we gotta look-
- Oh, oh!
- At the art in the back.
- The money on the floor.
The money on the floor.
- Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, as in like there's the
depiction of the-
- Mr. Washington.
- Declaration.
- Oh, like the-
- There's something framed back there.
- No, he said it's
featuring the whole tableau.
- Cuckoo clock here will probably open
and reveal something interesting.
- Sorry, what?
(audience laughs)
- This is probably a cuckoo clock-
- Ele.
- Ele, no, Ele.
- Okay, so, Ele I think
I've confirmed it's the spy.
- [Brian] Hey, Ele-
- Please show off your
answers in three, two, one.
Jacquis.
- I said the playing cards.
- Lily.
- The painting.
- Vic.
- That's so good.
- Cards.
- Ele.
- The cuckoo clock.
- And Brian.
- One of the playing cards.
- Something featuring an earlier tableau.
- Oh, it's gonna be the playing cards.
Oh, it's gonna be...
- Oh!
Oh, you were so right, it was the money!
- Somebody said money.
- Oh, it's on the back.
- I said money, I said it.
- Somebody said money.
- That's a $2 bill?
- A two-
- Is that actually
what is on a $2 bill?
- Dollar bill
and what is actually on it.
- Wow!
- Let me see it, let me-
- What is a-
- See it, let me see it!
- A two-
- [Ele] That's what the painting was from.
- Dollar bill.
- You're never gonna
get it back.
- Dude, I'm so stupid.
- Oh, the fucking, the old people.
- The old people?
- Would our spy please take a bow?
(Sam laughs)
- See?
- Would our informant please take a bow?
- Oh!
- Oh, this is...
- I'm an honest girl.
- And not me.
- That is going to be
points for no one except
for Vic who earns two spy balls.
- Love that.
- Players, please put on your glasses.
- Okay, okay.
- I wanna draw Vic
as a traitor.
- Let's draw me as a traitor,
and I drew them earlier.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Which is...
- Which is beautiful.
- Ooh, is the air
conditioning on or did I feel a breeze?
- That does feel like a nice.
- No.
- What is that from?
- [Ele] I don't know, I don't know.
Crack a yoke going on a
treasure hunt, X marks the spot.
- Players.
- Oh!
- Yes.
- Please
take down your glasses.
I spy with my little eye-
- Oh no.
- Something that wasn't
there a minute ago.
- Oh come on.
- Gotta be the mic.
- The mic was there but you
wanna know what was not there?
'Cause I looked at it.
That dart board only had two darts.
- No, no, no, no-
- Not true, not true.
- It definitely had three
darts, it had the colors-
- No, that had two darts.
- Spy, spy.
Were the dice-
- I think it's cake.
I think the boxing gloves is cake.
- And the dog showing ass was there.
- Which dog?
- Sorry, was his tail there?
- The dog showing, yes-
- Was his white tail there?
- The white tail was there.
- He had a white tail.
- Players, I'm gonna ask you
to lock in your answers-
- The piece of poop
on the tail?
- Just on the other side.
- In three, two, one.
- I wrote dice.
- Lily.
- I wrote three darts
'cause I knew Jacquis didn't write that.
- I wrote the dice.
- I wrote the die.
- I wrote specifically the D10.
- Something that wasn't
there a minute ago.
- Wait, but you've been
here the whole time.
- This dog collar.
(audience exclaiming)
- The dog collar?
- What?
- Sam, is that your dog collar?
- Man, Sam, you doing freaky stuff?
- Would our spies please take a bow?
- Aw, man!
- Unless I'm mistaken-
- Thank you.
- Our spies did choose the same thing.
- Goddammit, we did.
I chose dice.
- Darts and I did dice.
- I chose dice too.
- You did dice as well?
- Did you?
- I did.
- Damn.
- You wanted more points.
- And so no points at all.
- Okay I thought it was darts.
- Okay, I did that for everybody
so Vic wouldn't get points.
- Players, please-
- Dang! Drat!
- Put on your eyeglasses.
- [Lily] I really wanted
to keep the bit going.
- Yeah, this is, we've-
- There are like no more body parts.
- [Lily] Oh, except for
that one! (grunting)
- Oh, that sounded like
he touched your knees.
- Players, please remove your eyeglasses.
I spy with my little eye
a non-temporary tattoo.
- A non-temporary tattoo.
- I won't know unless I can lick them.
- [Lily] Wait, Brian, what
were you about to say?
- Oh, I was gonna say I know
this is gonna sound bad,
but I was the informant
and there are no spies.
So we should work really hard right now
to all do the same
thing and make it right.
- Hey, does somebody wanna wheelbarrow me
in that case?
- That's great, I believe you.
- Okay.
- Well, I'll wheelbarrow you.
- One thing that I've noticed
is everybody has light tattoos
that are kind of the same.
So it could be a red herring.
- Who?
- This has to be shoulder blade over here.
Y'all are right, okay.
- Now here's the thing.
- All right.
- I believe with all
of my heart that the art
department is so talented
that there is no way-
- This is adorable.
- Okay, 'cause the thing is-
- This is a full-on sleepover.
- There is no way-
- Wait, what shape is that?
That's not a bear.
- Those are the same tattoos.
- Wait, and nobody's face
paint is a real tattoo, right?
- These people don't have face tattoos.
- Don't say that.
- Stop it,
what are y'all talking about?
(clamoring about tattoos)
- What are y'all talking about?
- Players, I am going to need an answer.
- Give us a minute!
- You're so right!
- Going to need an answer.
- [Jacquis] All right, I'm...
- Show me your answers
please in three, two, one.
Jacquis.
- Instead of naming a tattoo,
I said the dog was the dalmatian.
- Lily.
- I guessed the dalmatian, but now I'm...
- But that's right.
- Vic.
- There's no people on
stage, there's only dogs.
(Sam laughing)
Yes, yes.
- That's wild!
- What do you mean?
- Ele.
- I'm going with the dalmatian's.
- [Sam] And Brian.
- I went for it, I said the
center is a face tattoo.
- Let's reveal our non-temporary
tattoo in three, two, one.
(drum rolling)
- There.
- The dog!
- That is a
wiener dog tattoo that is also
on our other two players.
- And it's put on all of them?
- I believed him.
- Informants, please reveal yourself.
- It's the truth.
- Brian was truth, we did say
there were no spies.
- I was honest.
- And so that is three
eyeballs for Jacquis,
three for Lily, and three for Ele.
- Just for the actors on
stage, I wanna know, like,
when you're in character, do
you think of yourself, like,
how are we thinking about this process,
I guess is my question.
- As a dog.
- Please put on your glasses.
- Okay.
- Oh!
(whimsical suspenseful music)
- [Jacquis] Ooh, this is a long one.
- Mm-hm.
- My ass.
(whimsical suspenseful music)
- [Jacquis] Lily, what are you drawing?
- You'll see, it's my biggest fear.
- Players, please lower your glasses.
I spy with my little eye: cake.
- Is it the cuckoo clock?
- I think it's just the cake.
- Okay.
- Vic is the spy.
Vic is the spy.
- I'm not doing this anymore.
(Jacquis and audience laughing)
- That thing with the cigar.
- Oh.
- I think that we should
have an embargo for content.
No content for this one,
let's just all write it down quietly.
- What?
- Oh, so this is the-
- So that the spy doesn't get it.
- We're not doing content anymore.
- No content.
- We're not doing content.
- DropoutTV,
we're not doing content.
- Content is being closed.
- No content.
- This will not be
on TikTok-
- God forbid.
- This will not be on Instagram.
- If you're scrolling and you
find this right now, scroll away.
- I do think it's easier to-
- They look the dice?
- [Brian] The dice or-
- I'm standing by the cake is cake.
- Players, please reveal your
answers in three, two, one.
Jacquis, what do we say?
- Is cigar.
- And Lily?
- I wrote cigar.
- And Vic?
- You bitch!
(Sam laughing)
- I wrote cigar too, bitch.
(Sam and Jacquis laughing)
- And Ele.
- Oh, the center bottle.
- And Brian.
- Cigar thing.
- The answer is in fact...
- It's cigar.
- Is it?
(drum rolling)
The cake?!
- You bitch!
- [Lily And Vic] You bitch! You bitch!
- I was gonna-
(Lily and Vic fake screaming)
- Guys, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Who put, did somebody actually put cake?
- No.
- Would our two spies please take a bow?
- You absolute bitch.
- You bitch.
- Absolute bitch.
- I wrote cigar.
- Guys, stop, guys stop.
- I will ruin your life.
- Guys, stop.
- No more content after this.
- That is unfortunately no points-
- Damn!
- For anyone.
- I can't believe that, I saw
that way before you called it.
You had something else written.
- Would the informant
please reveal themselves?
- Brian, would you like to
reveal who the informant is?
- The informant is Ele-
- I was.
- Who did indeed whisper into my ear.
- I have to tell you
right now, Vic is the spy.
And then I still wrote cigar
(indistinct) watching you guys.
- Ele, why you ain't tell me?
- Let's give it up for our tableau player.
- Bravo.
- Thank you.
- The points as we head
into round five of our game.
- Who cares about the points?
- Jacquis with 14,
Lily with 13.
- Ooh!
- Vic with 15, Ele with 13,
and Brian David Gilbert with 10.
- I shouldn't have done
the face tattoo, honestly.
I do regret it now.
- It's time for our next tableau.
- I'm getting addicted to this.
(all exclaiming)
(lively jazz music)
It's so good!
(players laughing)
- You said you wouldn't scare us!
- Behold, a New York City rat race,
and for once it's not a metaphor.
You might be saying to yourself,
"Sam, this isn't realistic."
But if you've ever lived in New York,
you've seen rats about this size.
Rest easy, players,
because one of you is now the leak.
- Oh, it's probably me.
- Okay.
- The leak knows
the correct answer.
- Okay.
- The spy wants to steer people astray.
- Yep.
- The leak-
- The leaks wants to give you the answer.
- Wants to give you the answer.
- Oh my god.
- If the leak guesses all by themselves,
they get zero points.
- No, Sam!
- So they have
to convince people.
- Otherwise,
they're scored as usual.
- Oh my god, I haven't
been paying attention.
- Damn, yeah, Ele.
(crew laughing)
- Players, please put on your glasses.
- Glasses, glasses, glasses.
- Oh, there's a baby.
- Okay, everyone draw a rat.
(whimsical suspenseful music)
♪ Nah nah nah nah nah ♪
- [Lily] Jacquis, have you
ever lived in New York?
- [Jacquis] No, but I've lived in Chicago.
- [Lily] Like with the rats?
Are there a lot of rats in Chicago?
- [Jacquis] Probably not
as much as New York though,
but there's a lot.
- Chicago,
they have everything there.
- All right players,
I spy with my little eye:
Brennan Lee Mulligan.
- [Jacquis] No, he gotta be like...
- I'm the leak,
and it's not what you think.
- [Jacquis] It's not him, he's not here.
- It's in the baby carousel.
I can't see it from here,
but I'm fairly certain there's
a Brennany thing in there.
- Wait, guys, but that guy
is sorta like Brennan's size.
- [Vic] This is what I'm
thinking, is like, I don't know-
- This dude right here?
- Brennan's busy today,
I promise you-
- He's not right here.
- We could get five points
if we just all say the baby thing
because I'm the leak.
Please just choose the baby pram.
We could get so many points!
- Okay, there is something
on top of that cake.
- I'm trying to help you!
- Okay, what's on top of the cake?
- I can't see properly,
but it looks like there's maybe
something on top of that cake.
- Okay.
- It is in the baby carriage, please!
- [Ele] There's something in the basket,
but I can't see what it is.
- I'm losing my mind!
- Like, I'm not like-
- I'm the leak
and it's in the baby thing!
- I'm not like, hold on, sorry-
- Just put it in there, "pram."
- Can you lift me on your shoulder?
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, I will do that.
Baby pram.
- Y'all see that little
action figure?
- Everyone do this-
- [Ele] That's what I was talking about,
I was like-
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- There is something-
- [Brian] Baby pram, do
you see Brennan in there?
- [Ele] You guys, Brennan, you guys...
He really wants it, maybe we
should just give it to him.
- 'Cause it's in the baby pram, I promise!
- But if he the spy...
- You don't think this rat-
- You guys-
- Is Brennan Lee Mulligan?
- [Jacquis] No, that's
not him, he would not
just do this part.
- If you're not the leak,
you have to do 200 pushups.
- That's not Brennan.
- I will do 200 pushups-
- Players-
- If I'm not the leak.
- If you're not the leak.
- I'm gonna need an answer.
- That's not Brennan.
- It's inside the pram.
- Guys, just listen to him.
- [Lily] Well, as long as some people
say baby pram with you-
- [Brian] We're gonna get points for it.
- [Jacquis] I think
it's the action figure.
- It doesn't look like him.
Go in closer.
- Let's explore the psychology
of why you won't listen to Brian.
- Please show off your
answers in three, two, one.
- Brian got me, I said the baby stroller.
- [Sam] Lily?
- I still think it's the chef.
- Vic.
- It's not the chef.
- Baby stroller.
- The pram.
- And what did you say?
- The baby pram.
- Let's reveal Brennan Lee Mulligan.
(drum rolling)
- No, that's not Brennan.
So mad that I...
- No.
- It was the (angry scatting)
- Why does he
have an action figure?
- What was this?
- I am going to-
- End you, Vic!
- Thank you so much, Vic.
Thank you, Vic.
(Sam laughing)
- I'm going to end you.
- [Jacquis] Thank you, Vic.
- [Brian] Vic, it was so good!
- Can our spies-
- Vic, you could have
gotten one other person.
- Can our (laughing)
- We both could have won, Vic!
I have to do 200 pushups now, Vic!
I will do 200 pushups
if I am not the leak.
- If you're not the leak.
- Vic, Come on! (groans)
- Brian had everyone on his side
and then Vic decided to vote with him
and cancel out all of his points.
- I love it.
- Why'd you do that?
- Players, please put
back on your glasses.
- I'm not gonna be a spy
this time, don't worry.
- What are we drawing?
- I think something simple like a spiral.
- [Brian] I think that's
the speed I have right now.
- Yeah.
- Brian, you got me.
- Ooh, that feels nice!
- That was really powerful.
- Wow.
- The thing is, I knew it was working,
but Vic, I didn't think.
I didn't think-
- No, I'm so sorry.
That was an accident.
- No, it was a good-
- Did you know that Vic-
- I'll never do it again.
- Was the other...
Did you know that Vic was the other spy?
- [Brian] I did, yeah.
- [Jacquis] So the informant know all.
- [Lily] It'd be fun if
some of the spies don't know
who the other spies are.
Is that a layer in the game?
- Can we change the game now
and go back and shoot everything
that comes to us?
- Players, please
remove your glasses.
I spy with my little eye
something that glows in the dark.
- I know how I was last time,
here's my spiral.
- I'm not listening
to anybody.
- But I do promise you
this time I am the leak.
(crew laughing)
And I know this is gonna
sound extremely bad, but you
have to remember how Sam is
and his tortured, terrible, mind.
It is also the Brennan
Lee Mulligan figure.
I know that that sounds ridiculous.
- No.
- I simply can't trust you
after what you did
to me last time.
- You are right.
- I will do 200-
- Today.
- Today, I'll do 200 pushups today.
I'll start my 200 pushups right-
- I simply will not-
- This is good.
- No.
(Sam laughing)
- I'm doing this for you, Ele.
- For what you did
to me last time.
- That's two, that's three.
Please, somebody get a count going, four.
- [Jacquis] No.
- Come on.
- 'Cause now he can be-
- Put one camera on
him while he does this.
- Yeah.
- Look, I'm-
- [Jacquis] I think it's those four stars.
- Oh.
- And when you turn off,
you know how you turn off the light?
- Yeah, yep.
- Oh.
- And the stars happen?
- Yep.
- See, that Brian lying, 'cause I said
the four stars, he was like, "Oh."
- That's what I'd play.
- That mean it wasn't
the damn action figure.
- Oh, I like that.
- No, I'm saying that's a great thing
for them to put on there also.
- Yeah.
- That is all, that, but I...
You point at the-
- I'm never
gonna trust you again.
- Players,
please reveal in three, two, one.
- I said the stars.
- Lily.
- I wrote stars.
- Vic?
- BLM figure.
- Ele?
- I suck at this game.
- [Sam] What did you say?
- You lied to me!
- The jump rope.
- Why?
- It's Brennan again.
- Brennan again, let's reveal
what's glow in the dark.
(drum rolling)
- Oh, man, damn.
(cast exclaims)
- The shirt.
- Damn.
- I don't know how familiar
you guys are with Dropout merch.
- I take it all back, all right.
- So you're saying I could get a shirt
like that at the Dropout store.
- Thanks, Ele.
(Sam and Jacquis laughing)
Would our spy please take a bow?
- I was the spy and I did a bad job.
- Would our leak please take a bow?
- It is me.
- That is two points for Vic
and two points for Brian David Gilbert.
Please put on your glasses once more.
- [Jacquis] Trust no one.
- Please don't
make me the leak again.
- We should write who we think is the most
untrustworthy person on set right now.
- Okay, all right.
- Okay.
- Just make it BDG again
and then this time we'll listen
and we'll know.
- Or not listen to him.
It's too hard to not be any of the people.
- Please put down your glasses, players.
I spy with my little eye:
a confetti cannon.
- What about those yoga mats?
- Okay, does a leak want
to reveal themselves?
- Yeah.
- I'll be the leak.
- You can't choose-
- You'll be the leak?
- To be the leak.
- I am the leak.
- Okay.
- No.
- I promise.
It's the cake, I promise you.
It's the cake.
- Oh!
- Why'd you say, "I can be-
- Because-
- "The leak if you want,"?
- Because after that
performance, I want you
guys to trust me naturally.
- Yes.
- Okay, I'm ready.
- It is the cake.
- [Lily] What if it's a rat's tail?
They're so thick.
- Lily, it's the cake.
- Please show me your
answers in three, two, one.
Jacquis?
- The cake.
- Lily?
- I wrote the cake.
- Vic?
- Drum.
- The drum.
- The quote unquote yoga mat.
- And Brian David Gilbert?
- The cake.
- Let's see that confetti cannon in three-
- It's the cake on the thing.
- Two, one.
(confetti blasts)
(chiming piano music)
(players cheering)
- I told you!
- That's nice.
- Three points for
Jacquis, Lily, and Brian.
Would the leak please reveal themselves?
- Hello, everyone.
- That's right.
- Beautiful.
- Why'd you say,
"Can I be the leak?"
- It worked.
- No one else.
- Players, please put on your glasses.
- Oh man.
(whimsical suspenseful music)
- Feel good about this.
- Next time they do it, I think.
- Yeah.
- [Lily] I think instead of
Caldwell, we'll all be drawing.
- Yeah.
- No, you can't catch me!
- What is going on down there?
- I think it's actually Ele this time
and she had to make a lot of noise.
- Yeah.
- It's random.
- That is true, it's random by dice.
Also, canonically, I think, hate people.
- Okay, talk to me, is it
dice is plural or is dices one
and the die is singular?
- What is dices?
(whimsical suspenseful music)
(Brian chuckling)
- All right, players.
- There is, I feel like there's
all three in this round.
- I spy with my little eye-
- Yes.
- Something for one of your homes.
- Oh, no.
- That is so nasty.
- [Brian] Oh, no.
- It's that red tambourine thing.
I don't know what that is,
but it's that thing 'cause I'm the leak.
- That's-
- I said it so fast,
you have to believe me.
- That's from my home.
- [Brian] The red tambourine thing?
- The red tambourine thing.
It is a food item.
You open it, you know,
it's like you make a-
- What?
- A thing with it.
- It is not mine, it is
Sean's, my boyfriend's, and-
- Boyfriend reveal.
- (chuckles) Spoiler.
- I do-
- Okay, okay.
- Look, I don't know what the fuck it is,
but I can't even describe it,
but I was pointed at it
with the laser pointer.
- I know.
- You open it,
it's an empanada maker.
- Ele,
I knew you was flagged.
- If we all write that
red thing, we can all get points for it.
- Players, let's have
you lock in your answers.
- I'll write it.
- Write my thing, I'm showing you.
- He is a demon, so I wanna
see what he's writing.
- I'm writing the red empanada maker.
- Then I don't know that I wanna write it.
- Okay.
- I'm writing it down
so that way I can answer-
- But why would I
show you this if I didn't write-
- What did you write, Jacquis?
- [Brian] I am saying it's-
- I wrote something else.
- What'd you write.
- He wrote drum.
- Show me your answers-
- You're not evil.
- In three-
- He's panicking.
- Two, one.
- I said the drum.
- Lily.
- I wrote the red empanada maker.
- Vic.
- Empanada maker.
- Ele.
- The empanada maker.
- And Brian.
- Red empanada maker.
- The answer is...
(drum rolling)
Ele's empanada maker.
(audience exclaiming)
(Lily cheering)
- Sean's been lying to me.
- Now Brian, that is going
to be four points for Lily, Vic, and Ele.
- Oops.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Ooh!
- God dang, I know, I know.
- Thank you, Nico and Ash.
- It's crazy that you guys have
people betraying people
in their own homes.
(Sam and audience laughing)
It's crazy that you guys made Sean lie
to me like that.
- Love this game.
- It's crazy that we do that.
A round of applause for our rats.
- [Jacquis] Thank you, rats!
- Bravo, incredible.
- There is cake, it was the pinata!
- The points as we head into
the final round of our game:
Jacquis with 17, Lily with 20.
Vic with 21, Ele with 17.
and Brian with 15.
- Five.
- It's time for our next and last tableau.
- I'm just here for the art.
(gentle music)
- Oh, it's all cake, baby.
- [Vic] It's all...
- It's Cake World, where
the grass is sponge,
the trees are frosting,
and the mayor is type 2 diabetes.
All rise for its national anthem.
♪ Happy Birthday to you ♪
(gentle piano music)
(Brian indistinct)
- No new roles this round, players,
just any number of roles-
- Don't copy that.
- We've seen already.
- All right, cool.
- Please go ahead and put on your glasses.
- Before this is over,
I'ma lick that toilet.
- [Lily] You've said that before-
- I know.
- [Lily] And this is the first time
it's been okay to do that.
- Yeah.
(whimsical suspenseful music)
- Players, please remove your glasses.
There is only one prompt
left of our whole game.
- One prompt?
- Oh my god.
- I spy with my little eye:
cake.
- Cake.
- Okay.
- Oh, man, which one is-
(audience laughing)
- You guys, I have something to say.
- [Lily] Yes, say it.
- I know what it is.
I'm gonna give you all
a little bit of time
to figure it out 'cause it's the last one.
The answer's really fun.
- Ele, stop.
- Ele, I hate that.
- Ele, stop, stop.
(crew laughing)
- Ele, just say what it is right now.
- [Jacquis] Stop.
- Guess, you guys should
guess around for a bit,
but let's just say someone here
is gonna be really excited.
- [Lily] Who's the informant?
- Oh, wait-
- Wait, who's the informant?
- I was not anything.
- So Ele, what are you saying
you are exactly?
- Who are you, who are you?
- Wait, "Somebody's gonna be
really excited," makes me-
- Who are you, Ele?
- Think it's the toilet.
- [Vic] The toilet, which is
making me think that's a lie.
- [Jacquis] It could be the toilet.
- [Ele] I'ma let you guys
play around for a little bit.
- [Brian] That toilet
looks like it could work.
- All right, I'ma join you.
- Okay, you kids have fun
over here-
- I'ma join you over there.
- I don't know.
- All right?
- [Brian] That toilet
looks like it could happen.
- I wanna eat that toilet.
- Jacquis, did you get tapped?
- I did not get tapped.
- It's the sink.
- Vic, did you get tapped?
- No.
- I didn't get tapped.
- [Brian] Nobody, did any of us get tapped
except for Ele?
- You could go
a little bit further, Vic.
You could go a little bit further.
- [Brian] Apparently, according to Ele.
- You could go a little bit further.
- I see the purple-
- I need more shoes!
I need more shoes!
- Okay.
- Somebody put shoes on top of my shoes.
- [Brian] Oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah, I'll get it.
- The icing on that toilet, it look-
- We got it.
- We got more shoe.
- [Brian] We'll get more shoe out there.
- [Jacquis] Like it's not
on all the way, you know?
- Here, we got-
- Vic, we got more shoe.
- [Jacquis] It look like paint.
- More shoe, ready, set.
- Forward, forward.
- Push up again, there we go.
- Push up!
- I don't know about this at all.
I don't know about this.
- Okay, quick, Lily,
we need more shoe!
- We need more shoe!
- Lily, your shoes!
- I don't know
about this at all.
- More shoe, more shoe!
- There are three-
- Come on, come on!
Put 'em on there!
- There are three
layers of shoes.
- There we go, ready?
Keep going, keep-
- The crew's shoes!
Get 'em, where are they?
- More shoes!
- Get my shoes.
- Crew shoes!
Get me the crew!
- That doesn't quite...
- More shoes, come on!
- That doesn't...
- Thank you.
- Pushing forward!
- That's all you have?
We need more shoes!
- Okay, now we have crew
donating their shoes.
- Let's go shoes!
- [Sam] Donating their shoes to the cause.
- [Jacquis] Keep going,
there's more shoes!
- Unreal.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
- All right.
All right, Vic, what do you see?
- The toilet lid does look plastic.
I can see the metal under
the trash can, so that's out.
- I told Brian what it is.
I told Brian what it is.
- [Lily] Brian, do you believe it?
- I told, you wanna know?
- Ele's the informant.
- No.
- You better get back
there the way you came.
- Okay, okay, Vic.
- Okay, Vic.
- Okay, okay.
- Vic.
- Okay.
- Come here.
- That's so good.
- Okay, okay, we got em.
- Come here, Vic, I need
you to see something.
- Somebody pull Vic back up.
- Why are my shoes
the only ones that are
past the velvet rope?
- [Jacquis] I need you to
see something, you ready?
- Yeah.
- Why did those ones have
to be the ones, thank you very much.
- Look.
- Players-
- [Jacquis] Look at something. (laughs)
- Do we really think that's it?
- No, I'm telling you that's what it is.
- Oh, I was the one that
was gonna be excited.
- (gasps) It's for me.
- I think that's it.
(gentle piano music)
(crew laughing)
Vic, it's always been for you.
- The whole time.
- Players, I'm gonna need an answer.
- We're down.
- Sounds great.
- If it's the boom mic, that is psychotic.
- No.
- Hey guys,
I'm glad we found each
other at the end of this.
- Yeah, this seems good.
- Please show me your
answers in three, two, one.
- It's the microphone.
- Lily.
- I wrote the boom mic.
- Vic.
- It is the microphone
because art would never let us down.
- Ele.
- It's the mic.
- Brian.
- You know it's the boom mic.
- Actual cake.
(whimsical suspenseful music)
- He can't reach that mic,
how can it be the mic?
- [Brian] There's no way, there's no way!
There's no way!
(Jacquis laughing)
- How can it be the mic?
- There's no way.
- No.
- Ooh.
- Okay, wait, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Samuel.
- Ooh!
- Oh man-
- Samuel.
- [Players] No!
- Stand up!
- No.
- [Brian] Colder, warmer.
- Samuel!
- Warmer!
- Yes!
- Warmer.
(crew exclaims)
(players cheering)
(triumphant music)
- That's so stupid!
(players laughing)
- I know!
- That's so stupid!
(Sam laughing)
- That is five eyeballs for every player.
- Yay!
(players cheering)
- Yes.
- The points at the end of our game:
Jacquis with 22, Lily
with 25, Vic with 26,
Ele with 22, and Brian with 20.
The winner of our game,
Vic Michaelis.
- Woo!
- Wow.
- Vic,
(audience applauding)
Vic, you win a cake.
(Ele gasps)
- Aw!
- [Jacquis] You win a cake?
- Unfortunately, it's fake.
- What? Oh!
(players exclaiming)
- Oh, yeah.
- That's so good.
- It's beautiful!
- Thank you.
- That's great.
- We're gonna share this.
- Before we end our show-
- I do want it.
- Players, let's bring
out our art and wardrobe.
- Oh hell yeah!
- Come on!
- Incredible art-
- Thank you.
- Magnificent!
(crew applauding)
- Bravo, thanks for the show.
- This was great.
- That does it for us
here at "Game Changer".
I am your host, Sam Reich, reminding you
to not judge a confetti
cannon by its frosting.
Good night.
(gentle triumphant music)
(gentle triumphant music continues)